theredx.com 2011-12-18

# Real Estate Data X-Change (The REDX) | Privacy Policy | The REDX

At Real Estate Data X-Change, Inc, we recognize that privacy is important.

If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, please feel free to contact us through our website or write to us at:

Privacy Matters  
Real Estate Data X-Change, Inc.  
2335 South State Street #100  
Provo, Utah 84606  
USA

www.theREDX.com  
support@theredx.com  
800-731-7339 

You may visit our website anonymously. However, when subscribing or using our services we collect information.

## Information we collect and how we use it

**Information you provide---** We collect information that you provide when you register on our site, place an order, subscribe to our newsletter, respond to a survey, and submit a question via the Contact Us page or by filling out any of the forms. We collect information, such as your name, e-mail address, billing address, phone number, and credit card information, so that we can bill you.

**Log information---** When you use REDX services, our servers automatically record information that your browser or REDX clients, such as our Lead Manager, sends while using our services. We collect computer identifying information, feedback you may send, service usage information, some information from files, such as CSV, excel, or text files you may import into the Lead Manager, or other information the Lead Manager may send to our servers. This information is used for purposed such as, but not limited to, personalizing your experience, improving our products and services, creating new products and services, account and bill for service usage, and to perform research and analysis of market and industry trends.

Your financial information will not be sold, exchanged, transferred, or given to any other company for any reason, without your consent, other than for the express purpose of delivering the purchased product or service requested.

Like many commercial websites, we use cookies and web beacons to enhance your experience, gather general visitor information, and track visits to our website. Please refer to the 'do we use cookies?' section below for information about cookies and how we use them.

## How we protect your information

We implement a variety of security measures to maintain the safety of your personal information when you subscribe to our services or access your personal information.

For example, all supplied sensitive information (e.g. credit card number) is transmitted via Secure Socket Layer (SSL) technology and then encrypted and stored in a database with restricted access.

## Do we use cookies?

Yes. Cookies are small files that a site or its service provider transfers to your computer’s hard drive through your Web browser (if you allow) that enables the sites or service providers systems to recognize your browser and capture and remember certain information.

We use cookies to help us track the promotion discount, if any; to keep track of advertisements and compile aggregate data about site traffic and site interaction so that we can offer better site experiences and tools in the future. We may contract with third-party service providers to assist us in better understanding our site visitors. These service providers are not permitted to use the information collected on our behalf except to help us conduct and improve our business.

If you prefer, you can choose to have your computer warn you each time a cookie is being sent, or you can choose to turn off all cookies via your browser settings. Like most websites, if you turn your cookies off, some of our services may not function properly. However, you can still subscribe to our services by contacting our sales department.

## Do we disclose any information to outside parties?

We do not sell, trade, or otherwise transfer to outside parties your personally identifiable information. This does not include trusted third parties who assist us in operating our website, conducting our business, or servicing you; or that may market pertinent real estate related information, so long as those parties agree to keep this information confidential. We may also release your information when we believe release is appropriate to comply with statutory law. However, non-personally identifiable visitor information may be provided to other parties for marketing, advertising, or other uses.

## Third party links 

Occasionally, we may include or offer third party products or services on our website. These third party sites have separate and independent privacy policies. We therefore have no responsibility or liability for the content and activities of these linked sites. Nonetheless, we seek to protect the integrity of our site and welcome any feedback about these sites.

## Children's Online Privacy Protection Act Compliance

We are in compliance with the requirements of COPPA (Children’s Online Privacy Protection Act). We do not knowingly collect any information from anyone under 13 years of age. Our website, products and services are all directed to people who are at least 13 or older.

## Terms and Conditions

Please also visit our Terms and Conditions section establishing the use, disclaimers, and limitations of liability governing the use of our website at [www.theredx.com](http://www.theredx.com/)

## Your Consent 

By using our site or subscribing to our service, you consent to our privacy policy.

## Changes to our Privacy Policy

If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes on this page, and update the Privacy Policy modification date below.

This policy was last modified on 01/16/2009
